More than one wears the mask.
Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse is a animation, action,
adventure film directed by Bob Persichetti.
Struggling to find his place in the world while juggling school and family, Brooklyn teenager Miles Morales is
unexpectedly bitten by a radioactive spider and develops unfathomable powers just like the one and only Spider-Man.
While wrestling with the implications of his new abilities, Miles discovers a super collider created by the madman Wilson
"Kingpin" Fisk, causing others from across the Spider-Verse to be inadvertently transported to his dimension.
Miles Morales (voice), played by Shameik Moore.
Peter B. Parker (voice), played by Jake Johnson.
Gwen Stacy (voice), played by Hailee Steinfeld.
Uncle Aaron (voice), played by Mahershala Ali.
Jefferson Davis (voice), played by Brian Tyree Henry.
Aunt May (voice), played by Lily Tomlin.
Spider-Man: Beyond the Spider-Verse is an upcoming American animated superhero film
based on Marvel Comics featuring the character Miles Morales / Spider-Man.
Directed by Bob Persichetti and Justin K.
Thompson from a screenplay by the writing team of Phil Lord and Christopher Miller alongside David Callaham, it is the direct
sequel to Spider-Man: Across the Spider-Verse (2023) and the final installment in the Spider-Verse trilogy.
Shameik Moore stars as the voice of Miles, alongside Hailee Steinfeld, Jason
Schwartzman, Karan Soni, Daniel Kaluuya, and Nicolas Cage.
The film continues from the cliffhanger ending of Across the Spider-Verse, with
Miles trapped in an alternate universe trying to save his family.
It is produced by Columbia Pictures and Sony Pictures Animation,
and is to be distributed by Sony Pictures Releasing.
Sony began developing a sequel to Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse before that film's release in 2018,
and eventually decided to split it into two films, which was revealed in December 2021.
The third film was titled in April 2022 and given a March 2024 release date, while early work
coincided with the production of Across the Spider-Verse before that film was prioritized.
The script and animation of Beyond the Spider-Verse underwent significant changes before
the 2023 SAG-AFTRA strike delayed production and its release date in July.
After the second film's release and the end of the
strike, work resumed in December.
The writers and directors were revealed a year later, and a
new release date was announced in March 2025.
Spider-Man: Beyond the Spider-Verse is scheduled to be
released in the United States on June 18, 2027.
The film explores themes of superhero, based on comic,
aftercreditsstinger, alternate universe.
The tone is thought_provoking.